어지러운 전국 시대.
The Sengoku era, a turbulent age.
카라쿠리인이 사는 지팡구국에서는 방방곡곡 접전이 계속되고
Jipangu Country, where the Karakuri people live, is a place of constant conflict.
카라쿠리 무예자들도 승리와 영광을 꿈꾸며 떨쳐 일어나고 있었다.
Karakuri Martial Artists take part in these battles, dreaming of victory and honor.
그리고 지금, 카라쿠리 무예자 제일을 꿈꾸는 터무니없는 영웅이 탄생했다!
And now, a wild hero has arrived, who wants to be the number one Karakuri Martial Artist!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi enters-dasu!
카라쿠리 검호전: 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden
Musashi Road
(The Story of Karakuri Martial Artist: Road of Musashi)
사내는 언제나 세계 한가운데서
A man always dreams of the day
제일 강해질 날을
when he'll become the world's
아! 아! 꿈꿔라
AH! AH! strongest
마음의 칼을 넓은 하늘로 번쩍 쳐들어
Raise your spirit's sword high to the wide sky
모험의 길의 막을 연다
Raise the curtain to the road of adventure
지팡구국을 떠도는 검호
A skilled Martial Artist wanders Jipangu Country
그 이름은 카라쿠리인 무사시
His name is Musashi, a Karakuri man
격렬한 칼의 소리가
An intense clash of swords
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸웠던 어제보다도 오늘 강해진다
Yesterday's battles makes you stronger today
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Art! Dual Blade Musashi
내일은 빛난다
Tomorrow will be glorious
격렬한 칼의 소리가
An intense clash of swords
눈부신 인생
makes life dazzling
싸우는 한껏 고요함과 함께
Fight your hardest with tranquility
무예! 이도류 무사시
Martial Art! Dual Blade Musashi
미간이 빛나고 있었다 무사시!!
Shining brow! Musashi!
카라쿠리인이라는 것은 지팡구국에 사는 슈퍼 인류이다.
The Karakuri people are a race of superhuman beings who live in Jipangu Country.
매일 무예의 실력을 갈고 닦으며 힘을 모아 승리와 영광을 위해 전력으로 싸운다.
They develop their martial arts skills every day and fight with all their power for victory and honor.
그 뜻은 명예를 위해서인가?
Are they looking for fame?
지금 온 지팡구국에 사랑과 우정의 혼이 작렬한다.
Now, the spirit of love and friendship bursts in the whole Jipangu Country.
대모험의 길로 떠나오!
To the road of adventure!
전국 시대는 어지러운 시기였지만, 이곳 츄고쿠 산지의 미야모토 마을은 평화로운 곳이었다.
Miyamoto village, located in the Chuugoku highlands, was a peaceful place, despite the turbulence of the Sengoku era.
이녀석! 멈춰라! 계란 도둑이다!
Hey! Stop! Egg thief!
도둑 아니오! 저는 알을 가져다 달라고 미와토루 씨에게 부탁을 받았소이다!
I'm not a thief-dasu! Miwatoru asked me to bring her some eggs-dasu!
미와토루한테 부탁받았다고!?
Miwatoru asked you!?
잘 모르겠다면!
Right-dasu! This is proof!
날 놀려먹을 셈이냐! 용서할 수 없다!
Are you making fun of me? Unforgivable!
무사시
Musashi
놀려먹는 것 아니오. 내가 지팡구 제일의 무예자가 된다면
I'm not making fun of you-dasu. When I become the number one Martial Artist in Jipangu Country,
열 배, 아니, 백 배로 돌려주겠소이다!
I'll repay you by tenfold, no, by hundredfold-dasu!
뭐가 제일의 무예자냐? 이 입만 살아가지고!
What kind of number one Martial Artist will you be with that wide open mouth!?
더 이상 못 달려...
My legs have given out...
오늘도 손님이 많이 오도록...
May I be visited by many customers today...
부탁드립니다, 지장보살님.
Please, heavenly saint.
가져가겠소!
Thanks!
야! 무사시 망나니 녀석이!
Hey! Musashi, you wretch!
-맛있어 보여!
-대단해!
-Looks tasty!
-Awesome!
지팡구 제일의 무예자가 되기 위해선 먼저 스태미나와 파워이오!
You need power and stamina to become the number one Martial Artist of Jipangu-dasu!
자, 모두 먹으시오!
Here, eat up-dasu!
네!
Thank you!
좋소, 잘 먹었다면 무예 단련의 시간이오!
Alright! Since we're done eating, it's time to train-dasu!
졌다!
I lost!
좋소, 다음은 제가 상대이오!
Good! I'll face you this time!
자, 어디서든 덤벼 보시오!
Attack me whenever you're ready-dasu!
아프잖아!
It hurts!
에이, 성가시게! 모두 한번에 덤벼들어 보시오!
Fighting you one by one will take forever, so attack me all at once-dasu!
그 때, 무사시, 열한 살. 미야모토 마을의 골목대장이었다.
Back then, Musashi was 11 years old. He was the leader among the kids of Miyamoto village.
아직아직아직! 자, 덤벼들어 보시오!
I'm still standing! Come and attack me!
괜찮아!
We're done!
뭐야, 겁쟁이뿐이오...
Is there anyone here who isn't a coward-dasu?
그런 거 아니야! 무사시 형이 강한 거야!
That's not it! It's just that you're too strong!
그런 소리를 듣다니 제가 더욱 강해진 기분이 드는 것 같소.
Hearing that has given me strength-dasu.
정말 뚝심이야...
He got the strength of beasts.
게다가 완전 밥보야.
And he's a glutton, too.
어? 뭐라 하셨소?
Huh? Did you say something-dasu?
아, 아무 소리도 안 했습니다!
Nope, not a thing!
아니오. 무예자의 귀를 간지럽히면 곤란하오.
I don't believe you. You shall not trick the ears of a Martial Artist-dasu.
분명히 뚝심에 밥보라고 말했소.
I definitely heard you calling me names-dasu.
무사시 형 화났다! 도망쳐!
Musashi's angry! Run for it!
네이놈! 달아나다니 비겁하오!
Damn you! It's cowardly to run away-dasu!
이건 사랑스러운 오츠루 씨의 비명!
That must be the scream of lovely Otsuru!
오츠루 씨! 오츠루 씨!
Otsuru! Otsuru!
아무나 살려주세요!
Please help, anyone!
이 미소녀야말로 무사시가 온 사랑을 바친 오츠루였다.
Musashi was devoted to this beautiful girl named Otsuru.
그 때 오츠루, 10살.
Back then, Otsuru was 10 years old.
멈춰! 멈추시오!
Stop! Halt!
무사시 등장이오!
Musashi enters-dasu!
오츠루 씨, 상처는 괜찮소?
Otsuru, are you hurt-dasu?
네, 무사시 씨! 고마워요!
Nope! Musashi, thank you!
별 말씀을! 연약한 소녀를 구하는 것은 무예자의 일이오!
Don't mention it. A Martial Artist must rescue girls in trouble-dasu!
무사시 씨 강하네요.
You're so strong, Musashi.
그, 그런 정도이오?
You think so-dasu?
강한 사람이 좋아!
I like strong people.
좋다니 그런 말씀을 해 주시다니 기쁘오!
I'm happy to hear that-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Musashi!
아니, 무사시라고 불러 주오, 오츠루 씨!
No need to say my name all the time-dasu, Otsuru!
무사시!
Musashi!
이야, 부끄럽게!
Oh, please!
뭔 소리에요, 뒤! 뒤!
What are you talking about? Behind you!
뭐오?
What is it-dasu?
이 녀석, 아직 살아 있었소?
Were you still alive-dasu?
하지 마요, 무사시 씨.
Don't do it, Musashi.
적에게 등을 보이는 것은 무예자의 수치오! 여기는 제게 맡기고 달아나시오!
To show your back to an enemy is shameful-dasu! Leave this to me and get away-dasu!
자, 일대일 승부를 보자!
Now, let's have a fair match-dasu!
이런 버릇없는!
How insolent!
무사시 씨!
Musashi!
멈추시오!
Hey! Stop!
멈추시오! 이 놈!
Hey! Stop-dasu! You damn thing!
야! 뭔 짓이냐!
Hey! What are you doing!?
사실은 세탁 싫어~
I actually don't like washing~
멈춰라!
Stop running!
어?
Huh?
아주머니, 위험하오!
Miss, get out of the way-dasu!
정말이네!
What on earth!?
무사시, 뭔 짓이냐, 이 쓸모없는 놈아!
Musashi, what are you doing, you good-for-nothing!
어이, 언제까지 계속 달릴 생각이냐! 곧장 멈춰라!
Hey, when are you going to stop-dasu? Stop right now-dasu!
어? 대체 뭔 일이래?
What's going on?
위험하오! 모두 비키시오!
Watch out-dasu! Everyone move!
코지로
Kojiro
위험하오!
Watch out-dasu!
비키시오! 다치오!
Move or you'll get hurt-dasu!
이것이 무사시와 코지로의 운명의 만남이었다.
This was the fated encounter between Musashi and Kojiro.
그 때, 코지로, 13살.
Back then, Kojiro was 13 years old.
까불면 다친다. 조심해라, 꼬마야.
You shouldn't act so carelessly. Be careful, kiddo.
꼬마라고? 날 모욕하는 건 참을 수 없소! 무예자라면 승부를 보시오!
Kiddo? I won't forgive anyone who insults me-dasu! If you're a Martial Artist, then I challenge you-dasu!
거기, 멈추시오! 안 멈추면 뒤쫓겠소!
Hey! Stop! If you don't stop, I'll chase you-dasu!
그만 못할까, 무사시!
Stop it, Musashi!
저 저런 아니꼬운 용서할 수 없소! 승부를 방해하지 마시오!
I can't forgive someone so pretentious like that-dasu! Don't get in my way-dasu!
입 작작 벌려라!
Shut your mouth!
이런! 아무리 타쿠안 스님이라도 용서할 수 없소!
You hit me! Even if you're the master Takuan, I won't forgive you-dasu!
-무사시가 있다!
-오늘로 본때를!
-He's over there!
-He'll face my wrath today!
무사시! 용서할 수 없다!
Musashi! Unforgivable!
아야야! 아프오! 비겁하오!
Ouch! It hurts-dasu! Cowardly-dasu!
-용서를 빌지 못할 망정!
-싸다, 싸!                -무사시가!
-You should be begging to be forgiven!
-It serves you right!                 -Musashi did it again!
그만두세요! 이제 그만해요!
Stop it! You've done enough!
오츠루, 이런 난폭한 사람은 맞아도 싸!
Otsuru, somebody so violent shouldn't be let off the hook!
그래, 이 녀석 때문에 닭장이 부서졌던 참이다! 오늘 절대 용서 못 해!
That's right, my chicken cage is broken thanks to him! I won't forgive him!
자! 대발로 감아 나무에 매달자!
Let's tie him up and hang him on a tree!
알았소! 빨랑빨랑 태우든 매달든 마음대로 하시오!
Sure, then! Throw me into a fire, hang me on a tree, do whatever you want-dasu!
좋아, 원하는 대로 해 주겠어!
Okay, then. We'll do as you wish.
용서해 주세요! 부탁드립니다!
Forgive him! Please!
분명히 무사시는 난폭해요. 그래도 날뛰는 소 앞에 뛰어들어서 절 구해 주었어요!
It's true that Musashi is violent. But he pounced on a raging cow and saved me!
대단한 용기를 가졌어요! 그러니까 생명은 살려 주세요! 부탁드립니다!
He has great courage! So don't kill him! Please!
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru...
그렇게 말하면...
If you say so...
어떻게 할까요, 여러분?
What should we do?
타쿠안
Takuan
여기는 일단 제게 맡겨 보시지요.
Leave this to me for now.
스님.
Master.
잘도 속였겠다! 타쿠안 마법 땡중 거짓말쟁이 땅꼬마!
You deceived me! Takuan, you stupid old monk! A liar! Dusty butt! A witch!
무사시! 천하의 넓음을 보고 머리를 숙여라!
Musashi! Feel the wideness of the world and be quiet!
반성하고 타쿠안 제일 싫소! 두고 보시오!
I hate self-reflection as much as I hate you-dasu! I'll show you-dasu!
나무에 매달려 까마귀 먹이가 되고 마는가! 질풍노도의 후반을 기다려라!
Will he end up being a crow's food, hanging on a tree!? Wait for the stormy latter half!
카라쿠리 검호전 무사시 로드
Karakuri Kengouden: Musashi Road
by Subdivers, checked by accelrandi
까불면 다친다. 조심해라, 꼬마야.
You shouldn't act so carelessly. Be careful, kiddo.
저 아니꼬운 무예자 놈, 키보다도 긴 칼이나 만지는 주제에!
How dare that unworthy so-called Martial Artist use a sword longer than himself!
언젠가는 내가 제일이 되어 웃음거리로 삼아 주겠소!
Some day, I'll become the best and make him a laughingstock-dasu!
배고프오...
I'm hungry-dasu...
야! 비린내나는 마법 땡중 거짓말쟁이 땅딸막이! 날 놓으시오!
Hey! Fishy smelling! Stupid monk! Shorty! Liar! Let me go-dasu!
조금은 반성했나!
Have you done some reflection?
반성은 죽어도 안 하오!
Never, even if I have to die-dasu!
오? 그 근성만은 칭찬해 주지.
Oh? In another situation, that's the kind of spirit I'd praise.
당연하오! 난 지팡구 제일의 무예자로...
Of course-dasu! I will become the best Martial Artist of Jipangu...
세상은 넓다! 너 따위는 우물 안 개구리 주제에 얄팍한 힘만 믿고!
The world is broad! You have as much strength as a baby in the woods!
만두 한번 맛있구나!
What a nice manju!
만두!
Manju...
시끄러워! 닥치시오!
Close your mouth! Shut up-dasu!
반성따위 할까보냐! 절대 안 하오!
Will I ever reflect? No way! Never-dasu!
무사시 씨! 무사시 씨!
Musashi! Musashi!
오, 오츠루 씨!
O- Otsuru!
무사시 씨, 괜찮아요?
Musashi, are you all right?
이 정도는 괜찮소!
Yes, this is nothing-dasu!
저, 부탁이에요, 고집부리지 마세요. 스님하고 모두에게 사과하세요!
Please, don't be so stubborn. Ask for forgiveness!
난 사과하는 일 따위는 하지 않소!
I don't do that-dasu!
무사시 씨!
Musashi!
지팡구 제일의 무예자가 되기 위해선 어떤 아픈 일에도 꺾이지 않소!
To become the number one Martial Artist of Jipangu, I will never break down, no matter what-dasu!
그것이 사내라는 것이오!
That's what it means to be a man-dasu!
주먹밥 만들어 왔어요.
I made a rice ball for you.
주먹밥? 오츠루 상! 기쁘오!
Rice ball? Otsuru! I'm so happy-dasu!
빨리! 여기로 던져올려 주세요!
Quick! Throw it up here-dasu!
이랴!
Here goes!
스님!
Master!
이 주먹밥은 내가 가져가겠네.
I'll be taking this rice ball.
스님...
Master...
야! 그 주먹밥은 오츠루 씨가 절 위해 만들어 준 것이라오!
Hey! Otsuru made that rice ball just for me-dasu!
너에게 이 착한 사람이 만들어 준 주먹밥을 먹을 자격은 없다!
You are not qualified to receive a rice ball from such kind person!
젠장! 도둑! 주먹밥 돌려줘!
Damn you! Thief! Give my rice ball back!
-내 것이오!
-전혀 반성하질 않는구나.
-That's mine!
-He's not reflecting at all.
-당장 돌려주시오!
-자, 오츠루 씨도 돌아가세요. 감기 걸려요.
-Give it back right now!
-Otsuru, you should go home or you'll catch a cold.
-타쿠안 땡중할배! 내 주먹밥!
-무사시 씨!
-Takuan, you wicked old man!
-Musashi!
멍청아! 구져!
Idiot! Uncool!
무사시 형님 불쌍해...
I feel sorry for Musashi.
무슨. 당해도 싸다. 알았어? 나쁜 짓을 한 벌이다. 너희들도 보고 깨달아라.
What are you talking about? He did something bad and got what was coming to him. You guys should learn from this.
참새 놈들까지 날...
Even the sparrows are...
멍청아!
Idiot!
젠장! 멍청이!
Damn you! Idiot!
신이시여, 무사시는 난폭합니다. 그래도 약한 자를 괴롭히진 않아요.
Dear God, Musashi is violent. But he would never bully the weak!
어떻게든 도와 주세요.
Please help him.
나 아무것도 안 할 테니까 여기로 와주시오!
I won't do anything-dasu. So please, come here-dasu.
혼자서는 외롭소....
It's lonely up here-dasu...
오, 좀만 더! 제게 앉으시오!
Come on, just a little bit more! Sit on me-dasu!
아직이구나.
Not yet.
나무에 매달린 무사시. 타쿠안의 용서를 받지 않고 계속 날날이 지난다.
Musashi was hung on a tree. Another day passed, and Takuan still did not forgive him.
아직도 매달려 있다니... 이대로라면 뻗을지도 모르겠네.
He's still there... he might collapse if he doesn't get down.
그래도 이 스님 아직도 용서 안 한 거 같으니 원...
But the master hasn't forgiven him yet.
악동이어도 아이는 아이잖아.
He's a brat, but then he's just a kid.
나 아무것도 안 하오. 그러니까 와 주오.
I won't do anything to you-dasu. So you should come here-dasu.
부탁이오... 혼자서는 외롭소.
Please-dasu... It's lonely here-dasu.
스님!
Master!
저걸 봐라.
Look at that.
참새가 저렇게나!
The sparrows!
강해지기 위해서 상대를 적대시하는 생각을 버리고 순수해졌다.
When he stopped being aggressive, his purity gave him strength.
순수하고 아름다운 마음. 그것이 참새의 친구가 되는 것으로 발전한 것이다.
A pure and beautiful spirit has given him sparrow friends.
어라? 스님!
Look! Master!
괜찮아. 모르는 척 해.
It's all right. Act like you didn't see a thing.
무사시 씨!
Musashi!
오츠루 씨!
Otsuru!
지금 구해 드릴게요.
I'm going to save you!
이제 괜찮네요!
It's all right now!
그래도 오츠루 씨 혼나겠소!
But Otsuru, you're going to be scolded-dasu!
아니에요, 걱정하지 말고 전 무사시 씨가 참새하고 같이 있는 걸 보고 정말 기뻤어요!
Don't worry about it. I was happy to see you with those sparrows!
그러니까 무사시 씨 사실은 정말 마음이 착한 걸 알겠어요!
You really have a kind spirit inside of you!
수줍소...
You're making me blush-dasu...
무사시 씨?
Musashi?
뭐오?
What is it?
이거 주먹밥이에요.
I made some rice balls for you.
오츠루 씨!
Otsuru!
스님도 알아주실 거에요.
I hope that Master will understand.
그러오.
Agreed.
무사시가 도망쳤다!
Musashi ran away!
빨리!
Quick!
꼭 꿈을 이루세요!
Follow your dreams.
고맙소. 전 꼭 지팡구 제일의 무예자가 되겠소!
Thank you. I will definitely become the number one Martial Artist of Jipangu-dasu!
오츠루 씨, 저... 저...
Otsuru, I... I...
네, 뭐에요?
Yes, what is it?
저... 작별인사를 해 주면 고맙겠소!
I... I'd like a farewell from you-dasu!
건강하세요, 무사시 씨!
Stay well, Musashi!
무사시 씨!
Musashi!
나, 최강의 무예자가 된다면 꼭 오츠루 씨를 부인으로 맞이하겠소!
When I manage to become the number one Martial Artist, I will definitely marry Otsuru-dasu!
그 때까지 기다려 주시오!
Please wait until then-dasu!
오츠루 씨가 만들어 준 주먹밥 정말 맛있소!
Otsuru's rice balls are the best-dasu!
그 때 그...
He's from back then...
잠, 잠깐 기다리시오!
Wait a moment-dasu!
기다리라는 건 나 말인가.
Are you talking to me?
그, 그렇소. 나, 무예의 수련을 위해 상대가 되어 주길 부탁드리오.
That's right-dasu. For my training, I'd like you to be my opponent-dasu.
얼굴에 밥풀이나 붙이고 다니는 주제에 무슨 소리를.
You have rice stuck to your face.
너, 아까 그 꼬마 아니냐.
Aren't you that kiddo from a few days ago?
꼬마 아니오! 난 미야모토 마을의 무사시이오!
I'm not a kiddo-dasu! I am Musashi of Miyamoto village-dasu!
나쁜 소리는 하지 않겠다. 마을에 돌아가서 밭일이나 도와줘라.
Sorry to say this, but you should go back and help with everyones's work.
네이놈, 업신여기지 마시오!
Damn you, don't look down on me!
승부!
Face me!
피해 올라가다니 비겁하오!
It's cowardly to evade an attack-dasu!
뒤에서 달려드는 것은 비겁한 것이 아니냐!
And attacking from behind isn't?
그건 아무래도 상관없소!
That doesn't matter-dasu!
머리 안 돌아가는 녀석이군.
What a dimwit.
그래도 이 미스터 코지로는 비겁하다 불리고선 그냥 넘어갈 수 없다!
But I, Kojiro, won't forgive whoever calls me a coward!
네 녀석은 코지로라고 하는 놈이오?
So your name is Kojiro-dasu?
무예에 뜻이 흐르는 코지로를 모른다는 것은 벌레라 부를지 바보천치라 부를지!
What shall I call someone who doesn't know of me, the famous Kojiro? A worm? A moron?
멍청한 놈이다!
A moron, that's it!
좋소! 명성이 높은 무예자라면 내가 쓰러뜨려 보여드리겠소!
Got it-dasu! If you call yourself famous, then I will take a famous Martial Artist down-dasu!
좋다! 무예의 길이란 얼마나 혹독한 것인지 알려 주겠다!
Sure! I'll show you the harshness of the road of martial arts!
무사시 등장!
Musashi enters!
비검! 츠바메가에시!
Secret Sword Tsubamegaeshi!
(츠바메가에시: 燕返し. 어떤 방향으로 내리치던 칼끝을 재빨리 번드쳐서 베는 수)
(Tsubamegaeshi: 燕返し. lit. Swallow Reversal)
안녕이다, 무사시. 바보 녀석.
Farewell, Musashi. Idiot.
야! 승부는 아직...
Hey! The match isn't...
말도 안 돼...
No way...
나... 나, 분하오...
I'm so embarrassed-dasu...
무사시 씨, 힘내요!
Musashi, cheer up!
오츠루 씨...
Otsuru...
무사시는 일어섰다. 그리고 걷기 시작했다. 그러나 수련의 길은 험한 것이다.
Musashi stood up and started to walk. But the road towards discipline is tough.
앞으로 어떠한 가혹한 운명이 기다리는가. 그러나 꺾이지 마라, 무사시! 앞으로 나아가라! 그것이 사내의 길이다.
What kind of harsh fate will be waiting for him? Whatever it is, never give up, Musashi! Keep walking to become a man.
두고 보시오, 코지로여!
You wait and see, Kojiro!
허공의 주머니에 달이
Sometimes the moon jumps over
뛰어넘어가는 일도 있어
the pocket of empty sky
큰 소리로 웃으면
Laugh loudly and
내일에는 아침이 와
morning will come tomorrow
잃는 것 따위는 아무것도 아니야
Don't worry too much about losing
계속 해나가! 앞으로 가!
Keep going! Go for it!
맨손은 강해
A bare hand is strong
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
인생 그런 거야! 기회가 어라,
That's how life is! Look, a chance
꼬리를 흔들며 쫒아와!
follows us wagging its tail!
그런 거야! 가볍게 가자
That's how it is! Let's go lightly
미래도 그런 거야! 내일이 어라,
That's how the future is, too! Look, tomorrow
양손을 벌리고 웃고 있어!
is opening its hands and smiling at us!
나보다 강한 놈이 있다니, 이야, 세계는 넓소!
To think that there's someone stronger than me, wow! The world is broad-dasu!
일이 꼬여 요시오카 도장과 척을 지게 되었지만,
Things get messed up and I fight against Yoshioka Dojo,
그 순간, 바람과도 같이 나타난 보쿠덴 선생님.
but Master Bokuden appears like the wind and saves me.
난 바로 따라가서 제자가 되었소.
I followed him and manage to become his pupil-dasu.
다음 이야기! 눈물의 수행은 배가 고프오
Next story! Training in Tears Makes Me Hungry
꼭 봐야 하오!
Don't miss it-dasu!
다음 이야기
눈물의 수행은 배가 고프오
재미있게 보세요!
Next Story
Training In Tears
Makes Me Hungry
We hope you enjoy it!